[{
    "question": "âš¡",
 "response": "âš¡" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ™Œ",
 "response": "ğŸ™Œ" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ·",
 "response": "ğŸ·" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ¶",
 "response": "ğŸ¶" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸª",
 "response": "ğŸª" } ,
 {
    "question": "âŒ",
 "response": "âŒ" } ,
 {
    "question": "âœ”",
 "response": "âœ”" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ—",
 "response": "ğŸ—" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ˜º",
 "response": "ğŸ˜º" } ,
 {
    "question": "âŒš",
 "response": "âŒš" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ‘€",
 "response": "ğŸ‘€" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ“",
 "response": "ğŸ“" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ¤·â€â™‚ï¸",
 "response": "ğŸ¤·â€â™‚ï¸" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ’•",
 "response": "ğŸ’•" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ˜",
 "response": "ğŸ˜" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ‰",
 "response": "ğŸ‰" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ¤³",
 "response": "ğŸ¤³" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ‚",
 "response": "ğŸ‚" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ’‹",
 "response": "ğŸ’‹" } ,
 {
    "question": "ğŸ±â€ğŸ‘¤",
 "response": "ğŸ±â€ğŸ‘¤" }


]
  
